Brad 猜猜今天收到什么邮件了
Yo, brad. Guess what came in the mail today.
死亡审判2: 死了别怪我
PENALTY DEATH 2：Excuse me while you die
- 预购.. 不不不-
- Preorder n No, no, no, no, no.
我可不这么说
Will not say that.
哦 嘿嘿 哥们儿 来了个新伙计 富兰克林
Oh, hey, man, there's this new guy, franklin,
我的新同事
Who just started working with me.
你们俩肯定是绝配 -瞧瞧，brad要给我拉客了
think you guys would be perfect for each other. Look at brad being my pimp.
是啊
Yeah.
是的 给他我的号吧
Yeah, give him my number.
酒呢  - 在这儿呢
Brew crew - right here.
我说哥们 你把污渍弄到我的东西上了
Uh, dude, you're dripping stuff on my stuff.
房规啊 你不收拾
house rule?if you don't unpack,
那么东西就是我的家具了
It becomes my furniture.
你把调味汁撒到乔丹上了?
You're gonna just spill pico de gallo all over jordan?
这也太不敬了吧
That's disrespect, man.
尊敬的话早就该挂起来了
Respect would be hanging that up.
兄弟 你是该解包安置东西了
It's time to unpack, bro.
你在这都住了差不多三个月了
You've been living here for, like, three months.
喂 你拿我的T恤当餐巾
Dude, that's my t-shirt that you're using as a napkin.
真的么? - 是啊
Are you sure? Yeah.
这不是餐巾?我还以为我们的餐巾都是V字领
It's not a napkin? I thought our napkins had v-necks.
神啊 我怎么会住在这?
No. Why do I live here?
你不明白 简 我被吓坏了
You don't seem to understand, jane. I am terrified.
彭妮  你没必要这样
Penny, you don't need to do this.
各位 我有话要说
Guys, I have an announcement.
我 我是来告别的
I've-I've come to say good-bye.
我已经做好了重要的人生抉择
I've been making some major life choices,
我决定离开芝加哥 -拜!
And I've decided to leave chicago. Bye!
出什么事了? -她有够荒唐
What's going on? She's being ridiculous. There was a break-in
她家附近发生入室盗窃案 然后她就一直说
In her neighborhood, and now she's talking about
要搬回去和父母住 -只是暂时的
Moving back in with her parents. Just temporarily,
等美国没有犯罪活动了再回来
until there's no more crime in america.
或者你可以像我大学时那样
Or you could do what I did in college.
勾搭一大群姑娘，还称作是“一个阶段”?
Hook up with a ton of girls and call it a phase?
哎? -那确实是一个阶段
wh? It was a phase.
这阶段可够长的 我想说的是去学防身术吧
Long phase. What I'm talking about is taking a self-defense class.
非常有能量的课程好不好
it's incredibly empowering.
而且你知道不?
Pfft. And you know what? You could really benefit
你真的需要多学学如何为自己说话
From learning how to standtap for yourself.
她说的对 彭妮
She's right, pen.
不是我说 你总是回避冲突
No offense, but you do tend to shy away from confrontation.
哦 彭妮 他们对你的车都做了什么?
Oh, penny, what did they do to your car?
能给我找两块零钱不? -可以
Could I get $2 back? Sure.
我的自卫方式正是回避冲突
In my defense, I do tend to shy away from confrontation.
哦 就是这样
Oh. Mm.
幸福终点站
第一季  第06集
==深影字幕组==
布拉德认为窝在屋里玩肢解巫师的电子游戏
So brad thinks it's harmless fun to sit around
是一种完全无害的乐趣
And play a video game where he rips a wizard limb from limb,
而我看看<特殊受害者>就是变态了?
But I'm the freak for watching "s.V.U."?
必须的 我最讨厌那些东西了
Totally. I hate that stuff.
哈!你被缴械了
Gi-gah! And you have been disarmed.
什么情况?
What was that?
我听了你的建议 我开始学马珈术了
I took your advice, and I've been taking krav maga.
这是以色列格斗术的精髓
It's this hard-core israeli martial art.
简直太棒了
It is the best.
我从来都没有如此自信 如此有安全感
I have never felt more confident, more safe.
而且我还激发了...
And I've really developed...
杀手的本能
a killer instinct.
亲爱的 你真棒
that's great, sweetie.
我应该有空跟去看看 -当然!
maybe I'll tag along sometime.  you should!
先告诉你一声 四节课之后
But be warned, in just four sessions,
温和的芝加哥人彭妮 哈茨
Mild-mannered chicagoan penny hartz
已经变身为
Has turned into
以色列的复仇天使 希拉 阿布拉莫维茨
Israeli angel of vengeance shira abramowitz.
哈! 把那个带去约旦河西岸吧! 衰蛋!
A-bam! Take that to the west bank, sucka!
哼!
Boom! Hud)
所以希拉是要买单?  -不不不
So is shira paying? Is that... No, no, no.
好 现在抓住那个婴儿然后砍掉它的手指
Okay, now capture that baby and rip its fingers off.
喔!红宝石啊
Oh, ho! It's spewing rubies.
是吧?  哦!停一下!
I know, right? ow! Stop!
马科斯!我又洗澡被烫到了
Max! The shower burned me again.
戴夫 不就是个淋浴么 有这么难吗
Dave, it's a shower, bud. It's not that hard.
放水6秒钟 跳进去
Let the water run for six seconds. Jump in.
你可以享受至少30秒钟的温水
You got at least 30 seconds of decent temperate water,
然后半转身 避开第一阶段的水锈大爆发
And then quarter-turn yourself to avoid the initial rust blast,
然后再回去冲30秒
Go back in for another 30 seconds.
他整的跟没洗过澡似的-哥恨你
It's like he's never showered before
哈喽?
hello?
嗨 戴夫 最近怎么样?
hi, dave. How's it going?
嗨 高音美女
Hello, high voice.
你是穿了紧身牛仔裤还是屋里进老鼠了
Either you're wearing really tight jeans or you have a mouse.
两样都有 而且相信我
Both. And believe me,
穿紧身裤爬这么高的凳子绝对是个技术活
It was not easy getting up on this chair. Can you come
你能过来不? -我觉得吧 打咱俩分手起
over? You know, I assumed I wasn't on mouse patrol anymore
抓老鼠这事就不归我管了 况且我都搬出来了
Since that whole thing where we broke up, and I moved
拜托啦 我看它是要长期定居了
out. Please? I think he's settling in for the long haul.
我看见它把一个肉丸拖到沙发下面了
I saw him drag a meatball underneath the couch.
戴夫 能把耳机拿过来不?
Dave, can you get us our headsets?
那个巴基斯坦的小破孩又上线了
That Pakistani kid biju's online again,
他讲了一堆的鸟语  -好吧 我马上就到
And he's talking a lot of trash. Okay, I'll be right over.
哦 你和富兰克林进展的怎么样?
Oh, so how'd your date go with franklin? Eh.
我钻进储物柜
I get in the supply closet
好半天才找到了钢笔
And finally find the pens,
所以最后大家人手一支...
And so it's, like, everyone has one now and...
干得不错 你开车来的?
Good, good. Did you drive here?
是啊 你想去兜风不?  -不
Yeah. Do you wanna go for a drive? No, I
我只是想告诉你你应该多喝几杯
was gonna tell you to order a few more drinks
然后你就可以把车开下悬崖了
Then ride your car off a cliff.
我以为你们俩很合的来
I thought you guys would've had a good time, you know,
我是说 你们俩都是...-我们都是什么?
I mean, you're both?we're both what?
超酷的人
Super cool dudes.
暂停 你本来打算说"同性恋"
Pause. You were gonna say "gay."
嗯 这样就讲得通了
Mnh-mnh. It all makes sense now.
你 我亲爱的兄弟 是个同性恋偏见者
You, my friend, are a gay-cist.
什么?  -你认为所有的同志都一样
What? You think all gays are the same.
你认为因为我和富兰克林都跟埃尔顿是朋友
You think just because franklin and I are both friends of elton,
Elton John英国天王歌手，是同志
我们就因该收拾收拾搬到佛蒙特州
We're just gonna pack it up, move to vermont,
VERMONT是美国最早的几个同性婚姻合法的州
然后开始倒卖古董?  -不 我可没这么说
And start selling antiques? No, I did not say that.
取消暂停 这没什么 别紧张 我逗你玩呢
unpause. Relax. It's fine. I'm just messing with you.
而且 有些陈词滥调也不是没有道理
besides, some parts of the stereotype are true.
我是说 虽然我们不来电 不代表
I mean, just 'cause we didn't get along doesn't mean
我们没有在班车终点站猛做爱   -真的?
We didn't have raging sex in a bus terminal. Really?
暂停 当然不! 由于你是个同性恋偏见者
pause. No! Playdate suspended
今天游戏到此结束
on account of your gay-cism.
恶作剧电话也取消了
We're not even gonna make prank calls today.
哥儿们 不是吧!  -好吧 就一个
Aw, man! Okay, one.
跟着我做 简
Just follow my lead, jane.
现在告诉你一个小诀窍，不收钱的哦亲
The key I'll tell you right now, this one's for free?
在于拉伸你的背阔肌
Is stretching out your lats.
那会让你的腿有更杀伤力
It gives you a little extra torque on your kill kicks.
知道不 我也听说过通过背阔肌
You know what I heard gives you extra torque as well,
可以增加力道
Is knowing where your lats are.
拜托 我知道我的背阔肌在哪
Okay, I know where my lats are.
嗯 他们就在
Uh-huh. They're right...
这儿嘛  - 好了 大家注意
Here.  all right, everyone, pay attention.
我是约尼
My name is yoni,
在希伯来语中的意思是"上帝的礼物"
Which in hebrew, is short for "god's gift."
很不幸 在梵语中 意思是"女性生殖器"
Unfortunately, in sanskrit, it means "female genitals."
我们现在开始分组练习简单的解除武器
Let's pair off and start with some light disarming.
每个人取一把橡皮小刀
Everyone grab a rubber knife.
好了 宝贝 我会很温柔的
Okay, baby girl. I'm just gonna take it nice and easy, okay?
我会把我的速度减半
I'm just gonna come at you kinda half-speed.
看招哦! 啊 啊
Here I go! Ow. Oh.
啊!啊!啊!啊!啊! 简
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Jane.
啊!我擦!
Ow! What the!
啊!啊!简 啊!  - 好样的 小美女
Ow! Ow! Ow! Jane, ow! Nice work, girlies.
好样的 很好 再来一次 起来 为了约尼
Nice work. Okay, let's do it again. Up, up, for yoni, ah?
来吧 咱继续 等下我还要上无痛分娩课呢
Come on. Let's get moving. I have a lamaze class to teach.
你确定那是个人工捕鼠器?
Are you sure that's a humane mousetrap?
是啊 我们抓到小东西后
Yep. Once we catch the little fella,
就到公园放生
We'll release him in the park,
在那儿流浪汉可以把它烤了吃
Where a homless man will barbecue him on a skewer.
啥?
what?
你得把那个修修了  -它折磨死人了
You should get that fixed. It's a total pain.
别担心 里面没鬼 我检查过了
Don't worry. It's not a ghost. Had it checked.
那就好 因为我正想问你会不会是鬼呢
Good. Because I was just about to ask if it was a ghost.
哦 我要去店里了
Oh. I gotta get to my shop.
你看把事情处理好后再走方便不?
Do you mind staying here and finishing up
还是你感觉这样有点奇怪?
And then letting yourself out or is that too weird?
那有什么奇怪的?
Why would that be weird?
屋子的每个角落我都赤身走过
Every square foot of this apartment has seen me naked.
这么一说就有点奇怪了  你走吧
Now it's weird. Go on. Get out of here.
好吧 拜
Yeah. Okay. See ya.
喔
wow.
久违的屋子呐
The old apartment.
不行
No.
大家好啊
hello.
马科斯 我告诉你 我不是同性恋偏见者
Max, I'm telling you, I'm not gay-cist.
是啊 好吧
Yeah, okay.
你是我的好哥们 你就是同性恋啊
You're one of my closest friends, and you're gay.
典型的同性恋偏见者的托辞
Typical gay-cist rhetoric.
你们这些人都一个样
You people?you're all the same.
"我们这些人"? 这才是种族偏见了
"you people"? Now that's racist.
让你尝尝我的厉害
I taught you how to eat a guy's spine, dawg,
你就这么对我? 兄弟 我心凉了
And this is how you do me? That cold, player.
好吧 你现在说话像个典型的黑人
Okay, you're literally talking
还说我是个同性恋偏见者? -哼!
Like a stereotypical black person, and I'm a gay-cist? Huh!
这太可笑了
This is ridiculous.
是吧 彭妮?
Right, penny?
彭妮?
Penny?
哦 天啊 对不起
Oh, my god. Sorry.
我就是有点神经质
I'm just a little jumpy
你老婆今天用假刀捅了我38下
Because your wife fake-stabbed me 38 times
哦 你忘了她的半周年庆生了吧?
today. Oh, you forgot her half-birthday, too?
她真是个禽兽 - 我知道
That woms an animal. I know.
哈喽?
hello?
嗨 是我 你抓住它没?
Hey, it's me. Did you catch the mouse?
还在努力中  -它真狡猾...
still working on it. Oh, he's a sneaky little guy...
哦 等等
oh, wait.
- 你逮到他了? - 等一下 我去看看
- Did you get him? - Hold on. Let me check real quick.
呃
Hmm.
不是 空欢喜一场
nope. False alarm.
可能明天还得过来
Might have to come back tomorrow.
呃 好像都已经有四天了 我简直不能相信
It's been, like, four days. I can't believe
你还没抓到那只老鼠 - 我知道
You Haven'T Caught This Mouse Yet. - I Know.
他就是我的本 拉登 杰西卡 本 拉登?
He'S My Bin Laden. Jessica Bin Laden?
我大学时遇到的一个很火辣的阿拉伯女孩
Super hot arab girl I went to college with.
呃 还是要谢谢你修好了橱柜
Hey, anyway... Thanks for fixing that cabinet, by the way.
- 恩 都修好了 - 还有空调
- Yeah, totally. - Thanks for fixing the a.C., too.
我还修好了你的环绕音响
I also fixed your surround sound
还带来了这个专用电缆
and brought this special cable
那样你就可以享受高清电视了
So you can watch tv in high def.
那很不错
- That is so nice.
- 你知道 我只是想把这变得更舒适 -恩
- You know, I just wanna make the place more comfy... - Yeah.
- 为了你 - 谢谢你修了这么多东西
- For you. - Thanks for fixing so much stuff.
好了 快走 快走
okay. Go. Go, go, go.
呃! 这真是太讨厌了
whew! Doesn't this suck,
这老鼠给我们带来的麻烦事还真多?
How this mouse has totally inconvenienced us?
简直是折磨
Torture.
你要不要开通橄榄球联盟的节目套餐?
Yeah. Hey, uh, have you ever thought about getting the nfl package?
我能打电话...替你
I can call... For you.
怎么了 亲爱的?
What's wrong, biscuit?
马科斯老是叫我同志偏见者
Max keeps calling me a gay-cist.
太糟糕了 完全不知道这个词是什么意思
That's awful. I have no idea what that means.
我以为所有的同志
That I think all gay people
- 会自动吸引对方 - 但你不是这种人啊
- Are automatically attracted to each other. - But you don't.
我知道! 但我喜欢他们
I know! I love gays.
希尔 斯旺克 汤姆 汉克斯
Hiry swank, tom hanks,
杰克·吉伦哈尔 威尔 史密斯
Jake gyllenhaal, will smith.
啊 你现在说的
Ay, now you're just naming
只是一些演过同志的异性恋演员
Straight actors who've played gay characters.
是啊 不过 拜托，表演本身就很GAY
Yeah, but come on. Acting is pretty gay.
怎么会出现这档子事的?
How did this even come up?
因为我想替他和我的同事富兰克林拉根红线
Because I tried to fix him up with franklin from work.
- 那家伙? - 是的
- That guy? - Yeah.
富兰克林 很无聊诶
Franklin's so boring,
我累的时候就会靠数他入睡
when I'm tired, I count franklins.
就像数羊一样
Like a... Shp.
呃 你为啥撮合他们啊?
so why did you set them up?
- 因为他们都是同志么? - 才不是
- 'cause they're both gay? - No.
- 等一下 你是同志? - 恩
- Wait. You're gay? - Yeah.
噢 那你真该见见我的兄弟 他也是个同志
Oh, you should meet my buddy. He's gay.
喔 我和一个有同志偏见的人结婚了
Wow. I'm married to a gay-cist.
才不是 你根本不...
That's not you don't...
我不是 我会证明给你看的
I'm not a gay-cist, and I'll prove it.
我会让马科斯看到他和富兰克林有很多
I'm gonna show max that he and franklin have
相似之处 不仅仅只是都是同志而已
more in common Than just being gay.
恩 那祝你好运喽
Mm-hmm. Good luck with that.
我得去上自卫术课了
I am gonna go get my krav on.
我和彭妮在玩的开心死了
Penny and I are having so much fun with this.
- 真的? 你确定? - 她都爱死这个了
- Really? You sure about that? - She loves it.
啊!
Aah!
干得漂亮!现在用她的武器打她
Beautiful! Now use her own gun against her.
- 嘭!嘭!嘭!嘭!- 太好了 简 很棒
- Pop! Pop! Pop! Pop! - Wonderful, jane. Wonderful.
你就像响尾蛇 又快又致命
You're like a cobra swift, lethal.
彭妮 你将有个人数稀少的追悼会
Penny, you will have a sparsely attended memorial service.
- 她还在动 - 嘭！嘭！嘭！嘭！
- She's still moving. - Pop! Pop! Pop! Pop!
- 噢! - 咔哒!咔哒!咔哒! 咋了?
- Ow! - Click! Click! Click! What?
嘣!
Boom!
- 嘣! - 好了 知道了 知道了
- Boom! Okay, we get it. We get it.
嘿 那奶酪是给客人吃的
Hey, that cheese is for the customers.
我也可以是客人啊
- I could be a customer.
你在一个强壮的男人面前穿过这个吗?
Do you have this in a men's extra husky?
你怎么又来了?
- Why are you here again?
- 有免费的无线网啊 - 哦
- Free wi-fi. - Right.
嘿 你见过 戴夫 吗?
Hey, have you seen dave?
我觉得他回家只是为了睡觉
I feel like he only comes home to sleep.
感觉就像和一个脱衣舞女住在一起一样
It's like living with a stripper.
他还在帮我捉老鼠
He's been trying to catch a mouse at my place.
还在弄啊? - 是啊 那老鼠很聪明
Still? Yeah, pretty wily mouse.
但还是有一点成效的
But it's kinda working out
戴夫 在等着捉老鼠的时候修理了很多东西
'cause dave's been fixing things while he waits.
而你根本都不担心吗
- And you're not at all concerned
戴夫 每天在你们以前的爱巢逗留  还成了
That dave is day-squatting and playing mr. Fix-it
- 修理先生? - 你要表达个什么?
- In the love nest you two used to share? - What you getting at?
阿莱克斯 我只是说 你知道
Just saying, alex I'm no doctor, you know that it's just
我感觉 戴夫 正在度过一段艰难的时期
That I feel like dave is having a tough time moving on.
他甚至都没有解包他的 迈克尔  乔丹海报
He hasn't even unpacked his michael jordan poster.
真的? 我是说他去
Really? I mean, heung that in his car
威斯康星公路旅行车上都一直挂着那个海报
On a road trip to wisconsin.
你不觉得他是在利用这个条件
You don't think he's trying to use this situation
- 让我们俩回到从前? - 噢 我当然这么觉得
- As a way to ease us back together? - Oh, absolutely, I do, yeah.
真的?
Really?
也许不是 我不知道 看着我
Or not. I don't know. Look at me.
我是个靓女
I'm a fancy lady.
- 那些是手镯 - 不会吧?
- Those are bracelets. -Are they?
- 是的 好了 - 你去哪?
- Yeah.Okay. - Where you going?
我得走了
I gotta go.
我要把鼻屎都抹到你的烛台上去
I'm gonna put boogers on all your candles.
戴夫?
Dave?
阿莱克斯
Alex.
嘿
Hey.
老鼠还在潜逃
The mouse remains at large.
我得保持静止状态
I had to be completely still,
所以我才躺在沙发上
Which is why I was lying on the couch,
我还得脱掉我的裤子
And I had to take off my pants
因为老鼠会听到我牛仔裤的声音的
Because the mouse could hear my... Jeans.
那是什么味道? 你煮东西了?
what's that smell? Have you been cooking?
我有些时间 所以做了一些吃的
I had some time so I thought I'd make some dinner.
晚餐? 听着 我知道这不是老鼠的事
Dinner? Listen, I know this is not about the mouse.
- 好吗? - 你知道?
- Okay? - You do?
是的 而且你不能再到这来了
Yes. And you can't keep coming here.
听我说 好吗? 你不知道
Just hear me out, all right? You don't know what it's like
真实的情况
Living without
别说了好吗? 马科斯 和我讨论过了
would you please stop? Max and I talked about this,
这变得越来越奇怪 - 真让人伤心
And it's getting weird. - It's miserable.
很多次我早上醒过来的时候我甚至都不想起来
Most mornings I can't even get out of bed
因为我知道等着我的都是灼热刺痛的一顿痛苦的热水澡
Because I know all that's waiting for me is A searing
scalding shower of pain
我能感受你的痛苦 真的但我
I feel for you, okay, I do, but I just
- 我现在不能这么做 - 我们可以的
- I can't do this right now. - We can make it work.
我想你该走了 走吧
I think you should go. Go.
有点小冷
It was chili.
五 六 七
five, six, seven and...
推!推!推!推!踢!
Push! Push! Push! And kick!
推!推!推!踢!
彭妮?
Penny?
- 然后 啊! - 彭妮?
-And then aah! - Penny?
怎么回事?
Wh-what's going on?
- 你说呢? - 像 "蚕宝宝"
- What does it look like? - Like "cocoon."
你不去自卫术课了吗?
Are you not going to krav?
再也不去了
Not anymore.
爵士跆拳道很有趣
Jazz kwon do is really fun.
- 而你把自卫课搞的太紧张 - 它本来就该那样
- And you made krav too intense. - It's supposed to be intense.
要是有人破门而入
If someone breaks into your house,
他们才不会用爵士风来抢劫你
They are not going to jazz-rob you.
他们会像抢劫那么抢劫你，甚至像杀人一样杀了你
They're gonna to rob-rob you or murder-murder you.
呃 我这么做是为你好
Okay, I am doing this for your own good.
但你摧毁了我的信心 你把我体内的shira都打跑了
But you, like, destroyed my confidence. You beat the shira out of me
行吧 好好玩你的舞蹈课吧
fine. Have fun destroyein your dance class,
当你觉得你的杀手本能回来的时候
And when you get your "killer" instinct back,
你知道我在哪
You know where I'll be.
- 在这儿我就能找见我的杀手本能 - 推!推!
- I can find my killer instinct right here. - push! Push!
好 护拳
Okay, and fosse fists.
八条密西西比河 九条密西西比河
Eight mississippi, and,nine mississippi,go! And...
十条密西西比河 转身90度 避开水锈
Ten mississippi, quarter turn. Avoid the rust.
呃
Ugh.
哦 哦 耶 我打败你了，死水锈
Oh. Oh, yeah. I got you beat, rust.
我打败你了 转回
I got you beat. And... Back in.
把管口调到90
Turn the nozzle 90 degrees.
这样就可以工作了 还不错
And we're in business. This is not so bad.
哦! 啊! 哦!哦!
Oh! Aah! Oh! Oh!
哦 天!哦!哦 天呀!
Oh, god! Oh! Oh, god!
马科斯! 救命! 马科斯!
Max! Help! Max!
在"死亡刑罚"里 你可以创建自己的角色
So on "penalty of death," you can create your own character,
所以我建了个葛林 贝克
So I made myself glenn beck,
glenn beck是美国保守派人士
所以如果我死了，感觉会很好
so if I die, I don't feel bad.
你为啥老是看着门?
Why do you keep staring at the door?
我没有 嘿! 看 是 富兰克林!
- I'm not. Hey! Look, it's franklin!
哦 布拉德 马科斯 你们好啊
Oh. Brad, max. What's up...
同伙么?
Home-homeboys?
嘻哈音乐 我很喜欢 你喜欢么?
hip-hop. I like it. Do you like it?
最近忙什么呢? 任何让
What you been up to, man? Anything max
马科斯 感兴趣的事?
Would be interested in?
呃 我买了一款新的杀人游戏
Well, uh, I just bought the new people-killing game
在X-box上玩的
For the x-station box.
我跟你说过我是电视游戏达人嘛?
Did I mention I was a video gamester?
我可能没什么机会
You know what? I Probably didn't get a chance to,
在我们聚在一起的时候说出那些重要的事
During our time together, divulge that important detail
恩 呃 那我今晚就睡得着了
Mm. Well, now I can sleep tonight.
哦!看这家伙 哦!
Oh! Look at this guy. Oh!
恩 我很乐意看到那样 噢! 还有一件事
Yeah, I'd like to see that. Oh! Other facts
也是那天我溜出去的原因 嗯 我喜欢
That may have escaped me that night, uh, that I love?
我喜欢 比如 我喜欢吃夜宵 这是其一
I love, uh, for instance, eating late at nigh that's one.
我喜欢带着芝加哥口音
I love having a chicago accent...
还有犀利的评论别人
And judging people cruelly. Yeah.
哇 跟我喜欢的都一样啊
Wow. Those are all things that I enjoy as well.
- 恩 - 不管怎样 呃 我得走了
- Right. - Anyways, well, I gotta I  gotta go.
呃 知道吗? 事实上 我得走了
Uh, uh, you know what? I actually, uh, gotta go,
因为我得去
'cause I'm gonna make
给种族饭店打个恶作剧电话
A-a-a prank call to an ethnic restaurant
顺便开发下骂人天赋
And exploit the language barrier.
耶 挺好玩的
Yeah, it's so funny.
人一旦变不一样还挺好玩的
So funny when people are different.
是啊 我走了 无所谓了
Yes. Yeah. So I'm out. Whatever.
没啥大不了的 谁在乎呢?
No biggie. Who cares?
再见
Bye.
这么好 这么成熟聪明
Good, old, awesome,
容易相处又值得深交的富兰克林
dependable, compatible franklin.
我知道你想做什么   - 马科斯  我只是
I know what you're trying to do. Look, max, I-I just think
你是想要我再给富兰克林
You're trying to get me to give franklin
- 一次机会 我会的 - 真的吗?
A second chance, and I should. Really?
对 你觉得我们三个一起出去怎么样?
Yeah. What do you say the three of us all go hang out?
好啊 你小子酷 我会安排的
Yeah. C-cool, man, yeah. I'll 'll set it up, bro.
这很酷哦 就你我和富兰克林
That's awesome. Yeah, it'll be just me, you, and franklin.
嗯 我是不介意做电灯泡的
Mm-hmm. I don't mind being the meat in that sandwich.
sanwich三明治也可指3P，不懂的意会
谢谢你让我暂住 阿莱克斯
Thanks for letting me crash here al.
对 我现在满脑子都是JANE
(alex) yeah. Jane has just gotten in my head so much,
我真的觉得呆在我的房子里不安全
I really don't feel safe in my own apartment right now.
没事的 你先回家 我就来
No problem. Just let yourself in. I'll be home later.
好的 谢谢
okay. Thank you so much.
- 没事 - 那好吧 我爱你
- You're welcome. - All right, I love you, al.
我也爱你 拜
You, too. Okay, bye.
- 拜  - 嘿
- Bye. - hey.
啊!
Ooh!
戴夫?
dave?!
是的! 戴夫! 就是我!
Yeah! Dave! Yes!
- 真对不起 - 啊 你在这干什么?
- I am so sorry. - Ugh! What are you doing here?
- 你在这干什么? - 我只是想洗个澡
- What are you doing here? - I want to take a shower.
好像能说的通一样，你到底在这里干啥?
Oh, yeah. Okay, that makes total ssense what are you doing here?
你有你自己的浴室啊
You have your own shower.
是的是的 但是我每次在马科斯那洗完澡后
I know. I know, but every time I shower at max's place,
我看上去都像
I come out looking like
- 短路的费舍 斯蒂芬斯一样 - 甜心
- Fisher stevens from "short circuit." - sweetie,
你不能一直说MAX的地方
you can't keep calling it max's place.
那也是你的地方 你总不能总是
Okay, it's your place, too. And you cannot break
闯入你前未婚妻的家去洗澡吧
Into your ex-fiance's house to shower,
因为这...你这打扮也太诡异了
Because this... This is just straight-up creeptown.
我知道 我明白了
I know. I gotta deal.
- 哦! - 你还好吧?哦!
- Oh! - Are you okay? Oh!
是的 我很好 我很好
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
虽然我觉得你把我的弟弟都踢成了妹妹
Although, I do think you kicked my "p" into a "v."
好棒，我做到了，真的
Nice! I did that. I did that.
或者可以说是希拉做的 谢谢希拉
Or should I say shira did that. Thank you, shira.
不用客气 彭妮
you're welcome, penny.
你喜欢鹰嘴豆泥吗? 嘿呀!
Would you care for some hummus? hiya!
不 佩顿 曼宁才是最有趣的
No. Peyton manning's the funny one.
- 伊莱是那个废话多的 - 好吧 对不起
- Eli's the one that can't close his mouth. Okay. Sorry.
- 嘿 老兄 - 嘿
- Hey, guys. - Hey.
收回这个吧 富兰克林 我带来个朋友
Keep it to yourself, franklin. So I brought along a friend
布拉德 我相信你一定和他合得来
Of mine that, brad, I think you will just hit it off with.
布拉德 我相信你会很高兴见一见玛丽女士的
Brad, I'd like you to meet miss mary.
我在我家的门前遇见她正在卖圣经
I met her on my floor, selling bibles,
我觉得你们俩有许多神似之处
And I thought, you guys got a lot in common.
很高兴见到你 布拉德
- So nice to meet you, brad.
我也是 - 玛丽女士你是不是需要坐下
Ma'am. - Miss marhy don't you have a seat
和布拉德多聊聊啊
and tell brad some more
关于为什么你的宗教信仰不信任输血?
About how your religion doesn't believe in blood transfusions?
哦 好吧
Oh, sure.
恩 无意冒犯  玛丽女士 但是 马科斯
Um, no offense, miss mary, but, uh, max,
你到底觉得我和这位女士有什么共同之处?
What on earth do you think I have in common with this woman?
- 为什么我觉得你们俩合得来? - 是的
- Why do I think you have something in common with her? - Yeah.
我不知道 但是
I don't know, 'cause...
你们俩都
You're both...
好吧 我是一个同性恋偏见者
okay, I'm a gay-cist.
早该这样了嘛，得写张大字报贴出去
There it is. Put it on the board.
你和富兰克林 没有任何相似的
-  yo and franklin Have nothing in common
- 除了性取向 - 没关系 布拉德
- except your sexual preference. - It's all right, brad.
我和富兰克林昨天仍然在浴室大战了300回合
Me and franklin still had raging sex in the bathroom.
- 你们俩在浴室里激情做爱? - 当然没有
- You guys had rocking, gay sex in the bathroom? - No! Ugh!
你们俩可以手牵手一起下地狱了
You boys are going straight to hell in a handbasket
迅速的猛抓那个美国佬的蛋蛋
And with one swift yank of the testicles...
嘿!
Hey!
我的杀手天性回来了
I got my killer instinct back.
我雄起了一把，然后昨天晚上我狠狠揍了DAVE一顿
I stood up for myself, and last night, I beat dave's ass!
现在老娘来找你算账了
And now I've come for you.
这次我知道我的背阔肌在哪里了
And this time, I know where my lats are.
嘣!
Boom!
还是不对，你真的揍了DAVE?就是我们的那个朋友DAVE？
Still no. And you beat dave, our friend, up?
闭嘴，竹竿妹，这是个游戏，现在开始计时
Shut your mouth, scarecrow. It is game, set, go time.
我和你的比赛
Match you and me.
戴夫 我们得谈谈 我在想
Dave, we need to talk. I was thinking about it,
那天我把你赶出去的方式
And the way I kicked you out the other day鈥?
- 非常的粗鲁 - 没事 我理解
That was really rude. - It's okay. I understand.
不 是我太自私了 我只是不喜欢你在修东西
No, I was being selfish. Okay? I just don't really liked the way...
而我一直在不停的想着
That you were fixing stuff, and I didn't stop think
那些会唤起我对你的感情的东西
About how that might reawaken all those feelings in you.
感情?
- Feelings?
相信我 我对你的感情也很复杂的
Trust me. I have complicated feelings about you, too.
我只是觉得现在不是一个
I just don't think now is the right time
让我们重新复合的好时机 -哦!
To try and get back together. Oh! (chuckles)
不 不 我才不想再和你复合呢
no, no. I don't want to get back togher.
不 我唯一想要复合的是
No, the only thing I wanted to get back together with
我的旧淋浴
Was my old shower.
真的吗? 等等 难道你想让我相信
Really? Wait. You expect me to believe that you basically
你偷偷进我的房子就是为了我的淋浴
Moved back into my apartment because you love my shower?
是的 因为它很干净
Yeah, because it's clean,
还因为你有蝴蝶形状的肥皂
Because you have soap that's shaped like butterflies.
而这里的肥皂就像是十五个迷你的粘在一起
Here, the soap is shaped like 15 mini soaps smasd together
- 还用头发扎了起来 - 你可以买块新的啊
- And wrapped in hair. - You know you can just buy soap.
阿莱克斯 我发誓我对你的感情没有死灰复燃
Alex, I swear I don't have any reawakened feelings.
- 我知道 -  不像你
- I know. - Unlike you...
明显是完全死灰复燃了
Hmm? Who apparently is fully awake.
什么? 什么? 怎么可能
What? What? No.
我才不会呢 绝不可能 哼哼
I'm not awake at all. Nope. Mnh-mnh.
- 你到底在我的公寓里干嘛? - 尝试
- What are you doing in my apartment? Trying to figure out
从Dvr中删掉12小时的足球比赛
How to delete 12 hours of nfl football off dvr.
原来这样啊
Oh.
什么时候这成了你的地方?
Since when are you calling this your place?
好吧 尽管有点乱 但毕竟是个家
Well, it is gnarly, but it's home.
是 是不赖啊
Well, not quite.
我来帮你挂这个
I could help you hang this.
我自己学会了怎么样钉钉子
I taught mysel how to hammer a nail.
你知道嘛
um, you know...
你不能把钉子定在砖头上 你知道的 对吧?
You can't hammer nails into brick. You know that, right?
恩我知道  在这似乎好看点
Yeah. Mm-hmm. Looks better here.
你真的能处理好你那些始终困扰你的
You gonna be able to decorate with all these feelings
- 感情问题吗? - 嘿 闭嘴
- Dancing around your head? - Hey, shut up.
这个呢 复杂的东西?
Does this...  complicate things?
- 什么? - 这个
- Excuse me? - This.
没看懂
I don't understand that. (books thud)
- 那这样呢? - 哇!爹啊
- What about this? Mm! Whew, boy.
- 那这样呢? - 这个有点难
- What about this? - That is complicated.
别把桌子推翻了
Don't pull something.
- 你确定你要这么做? - 恩
- You sure you wanna do this? - Uh-huh.
我可不会手软的 彭妮
'cause I'm not gonna hold back, penny.
谁是彭妮? 我可是希拉...
Who's penny? My name is shira...
- 加油 希拉! - 我来了!
- go, shira! - Abramowitz!
啊 我为你骄傲 彭妮 你的杀手本色回来了
aah! I'm proud of you, pen. You got your killer instinct back.
但不意味这你就能赢我
But it doesn't mean I still don't own you in krav.
哦!
oh!
打她! 打她!
Get her! Get her!
再暴力点就跟你们是黑社会的一样
More ruthless, like you're a gang member.
很好 摔得好 我喜欢
good. Good twist. I like it.
我戳死你!
I stab you!
我有强力护盾
I have a force field!
好的  简 拿起那把木枪
okay, jane, get the wooden gun!
砰! 砰! 砰!
Pop! Pop! Pop!
砰! 砰! 砰! 砰!
pop! Pop! Pop! Pop!
子弹时间
I'm deflecting bullets!
砰! 砰!
Pop! Pop!
砰!  啊!
Pop! Aah!
下勾拳
fosse fists.
下勾拳是神马东东?
What the hell is a fosse fist?
去死吧!
Sucka!
打倒你的是自卫术
It was the krav maga that might have beaten you,
但是爵士跆拳道让这个过程赏心悦目
But it was the jazz kwon do that made it look so fine.
爵士跆拳道?
jazz kwon do?
我需要在哪报名呢?
Where do I sign up?
是的
yeah.
动作很棒 我为你骄傲 你刚才确实很牛逼
Really great moves. I'm so pro of you. You were great up there.
伙计们 我发誓 这不是训练
Guys, I promise u, this is not a drill.
好吧 大伙们 站好队
okay, guys. Let's get into formation.
四 五 六 七 八 孔雀开屏
Four, five, six, seven, eight. Grab your tiny hat.
伸展运动 伸展运动
Fosse fists. Fosse fists. Fosse fists. Fosse fists.
猴子偷桃
yeah.
来 嘣
ah, boom.
恩 很好
Yeah. Okay.
挥手 挥手
Hat. Hat, hat, hat.
驴踢! 嘿呀!
Krav!  hiya!
回到中间
Bring it back to center.
享受一下  快速休息下
Have a little fun and take a quick break.
好再来
And now back.
后退后退  哇唔!
Back it back it up. Whoa!
跳大神!跳大神
We're here! Push!
抽筋 抽筋 使劲抽
Shimmy, shimmy.
我擦 我擦 我擦擦擦
(all) no! No! No! No!
好的！
Yes!
嘘!  哦 上帝啊
Shh! oh, god, no.
再来一遍  再来一遍 呼!
We're going again. We are going again. Whoo!
我爱这种能量 现在知道了 全部忘记 继续
I like t energy. Now you know it. Now forget it.